petrolstationsforsale.co.za 2017-05-24

# Cyrus Business Brokers South Africa - Privacy Policy

**Cyrus Business Brokers** ** & Associates** and all related companies, take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our  **Privacy Policy**.  **Protecting your information**  
**Cyrus Business Brokers**  values the users of our website. We esteem your privacy and believe and consider it an significant part of our business.  We recognize that you may be worried about our collection, use, and revelation of the in person identifiable data that we collect when you use/browse our website. By utilising the website you are accepting our principles and practices as recounted in this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at  **[info@petrolstationsforsale.co.za](mailto:andre@petrolstationsforsale.co.za).**

**Personal data assembled**  
We collect personal information from you only if you provide it voluntarily. This data cannot and does not identify you individually. We assemble and sustain certain individual information about you when you entire any of our online types or drive us an internet message. The information you provide can identify you individually and encompasses items such as your name and email address and is utilised to drive demanded data and to reply to enquiries. 

**Information**

 **assembled and stored mechanically**  
If you visit our website just to browse, read pages or download data, we accumulate and shop certain data about your visit mechanically. This data cannot and does not identify you individually. We assemble and sustain certain individual information about you when you entire any of our online types or drive us an internet message. The information you provide can identify you individually and encompasses items such as your name and email address and is utilised to drive demanded data and to reply to enquiries. The kind of data that is gathered mechanically include the designated day and time of your visit and the sheets you visit. We occasionally use this non-personally identifiable data to improve our website content that finally gives you a better browsing know-how.  
  
**Links to Other Sites**  
Our website sometimes comprises connections to other websites whose privacy policies may be different to ours. The privacy principles of these websites are not under our control. one time you leave our servers, use of any data you supply is governed by the privacy principle of the operator of the site you are visiting. tourists should confer the other sites' privacy notices as we have no control over the data that is submitted to, or assembled by, these third parties.

**Alterations in Privacy Principle**

The policy may change from time to time; so delight ascertain it occasionally. express gratitude you for taking the time to read our Privacy principle.

**Do you have any additional inquiries?    
**If you have any inquiries or concerns, delight communicate us at +27 (0)12 333 9042 or 

**info@petrolstationsforsale.co.za**
